=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 19=
The Divine Stone belongs to me.
You
are mine as well.
Chi Xiao.
Chi...
Chi Xiao?
No.
That is not Chi Xiao.
He is Yu Linjun,
ruler of the Void Realm.
Ruler of the Void Realm, so what?
if you kneel and submit,
I
may spare your life.
A mere mortal
daring to wield our forbidden arts.
Such flesh and blood,
I truly cannot wait to taste it.
You dared to kill my vessel
that I sent to find the Stone
in the mortal world.
You have no idea
what you've brought upon yourself.
Since you have come to me today,
I don't even need to hunt you down.
For all those scores and grudges
today, I will make you pay.
If I could travel freely
to the mortal world,
do you think I would have let you go?
(I can't even touch her...)
You seem stronger now.
That only makes me want you more.
I can't wait to taste you.
Ziyan! Ziyan!
Ziyan!
Have you made your choice?
Use the Wind God Chronicle
and my life as the vessel
to extract the Stone from her,
and mend the sky with it.
The Chronicle will stay within her.
And no one will be able
to harm her again.
For everything you have done,
do you have any regrets?
This time,
you don't seem angry.
Through all of this,
I am glad it was you I met.
Farewell.
The road ahead...
you walk alone.
Ziyan.
Ziyan!
Yuanchu.
Ziyan is in danger.
I have to go save her.
Yuanchu.
Ziyan is in danger.
You have been unconscious for days.
The Void Realm has descended.
The mortal world is in chaos.
Demons rule.
Humans suffer.
You've lost the Wind God Chronicle,
and your meridians are damaged.
I can't let you risk yourself.
The spell has faded.
The connection is gone.
Something must have happened to Ziyan.
Ziyan,
she is marrying Yu Linjun in three days.
Yuanchu, she shielded you
in that barrier
because she didn't want you to get hurt.
Listen to me,
heal your wounds first.
Then I'll go with you
to crash that wedding.
Senior...
It is all right.
My meridians are severed,
I'll just have to rebuild them.
Senior,
Yuanzhen Sect is protected by a barrier.
Demons cannot enter for now.
You focus on your recovery.
This time,
I will not lose her again.
Ziyan,
you are awake.
Lanxi!
Is it really you?
It is me.
What is wrong?
Did you have another nightmare?
(It cannot be.)
(My sister was killed by Yu Linjun...)
(What is really going on?)
(Why can't I remember anything?)
Don't cry.
Look! This is the gift you gave me.
Do you still remember?
You said it looked like a butterfly
breaking free.
You hoped we would be free like it.
Put it on for me.
Like you used to.
Why are you crying?
I'm right here.
Lanxi.
I missed you so much.
I thought I had lost you forever.
Silly girl.
Yu Linjun brought me back.
Yu Linjun?
Mm.
Here he comes.
My Lord.
Hm.
The Demon Queen tried to kill me
to avenge you.
Now that your sister is alive again,
I have given you two this reunion.
All grievances between us are settled.
So now, can you love me?
Ridiculous.
- Someone like you...
- Ziyan...
My Lord and Ziyan
are a perfect match.
Lanxi.
From now on, I will ensure you both
live in wealth and honor.
Across both realms,
only I will stand above you.
(No matter.)
(I will find a way to touch you)
(and claim you.)
(That crack looks just like
my Stone Curse mark.)
(Lanruo Hall)
He revived me for you.
And now he has reopened
Lanruo Hall for you.
I've never seen Yu Linjun
care so much for any Saintess.
You should cherish this.
He has no heart.
Lanxi, you used to hate him.
How can you forgive him so easily?
Has he bewitched you?
I just think
that living well matters most.
Now we have his protection.
We can finally live with dignity.
No more fear and suffering.
No more hardship.
Isn't that good?
Promise me, Ziyan,
Stop fighting Yu Linjun.
(Don't drink too much, now.)
(Only you spoil me like this.)
(Let's go upstairs.)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪